ALEXANDER BERG

QA Engineer

Junior Quality Assurance engineer with IT knowledge. Finished online university QA program. IT geek for 12 years. Looking forward to joining a company and use my creativity and experience to improve the overall quality of a product or service. All my skills, code and contacts on my personal web-site.

CONTACT INFORMATION

Email

alexandr.berg92@gmail.com

Address

Saint Petersburg, Russia

Phone

+79062452865

Date of birth

Jun 22, 1992

Link

alexander-berg.github.io

SKILLS

- Working knowledge of Web Automation
- Excellent analytical skills
- Experienced in bug reporting and finding errors
- Multiple IT skills
- Covid-19 certificate

LANGUAGES

English

Advanced

Russian

Native



EXPERIENCE

2018 - 2020

Alpha tester

Ubisoft, Wargaming

Tested games like "World of warships", "For Honor", "Anno" in closed alpha programs, created bug-reports

Saint Petersburg 2016 - 2018 Sales Assistant
OOO "Palmira"

Engaged in sales of digital equipment, smartphones, laptops and services

Saint Petersburg 2014 - 2015 Low current systems engineer assistant OOO "Bors"

Was engaged in the installation of low-current security and fire safety systems

Saint Petersburg 2013 - 2014 • Technical Support
OOO "Teletrade"

Assisting clients with complex technical issues requiring in-depth problem solving

EDUCATION

2020 - 2021

QA engineer

Netology Online university

Studied Software development, software testing, Java, C#, CI/CD, tests automation.

Saint Petersburg 2012 - 2013 Municipal & government managment

Herzen State University

Saint Petersburg 2010 - 2011 Meteorologist

Russian State Hydrometeorological University